so very similar to the last Apple is
Apple number six which is comparing
solutions so we all need and starts out
very simple
we all need food clothing shelter and
other things like connection and
happiness but just food clothing shelter
energy waste disposal we all have those
needs that need to be met and just to
live basically and so finding the
solutions that already exist in those
fields and comparing them if I wanted to
have water Dyke wipe water water is
clearly also a necessity do I want if I
want clean water how do I get it and
where I currently am it involves turning
on the tap and then I filter my water
which probably isn't even super
necessary since I live in one of the
best cities in the world for water but I
still do and but what does that entail
is my water system the best is my filter
for the price that I get and the water
quality I don't know I have no idea I
just go off with their branding and that
they're like decently priced and not
astronomically about thousands of
dollars but not you know Burnett ten
dollars which I mean Brit is better than
nothing and I don't know maybe Brit is
better than the one I have that I'm
spending too much money but comparing
them and so if you are starting a new
community in the middle of nowhere with
an intentional community how do you get
water how do you create and there's tons
of ways to do that there's tons of
things that filter water and store water
and with water through but what's the
best solution for you to implement the
first cost as well as the cost of
maintenance is it easily maintained is
to do it yourself do you have to go
through the company is it to
technological tool to compare the
solutions so that anyone anywhere in the
world can go on and say ok price-wise
what's the best solution for me because
like if I can create it for 30 dollars
from what I have around great if I need
to spend ten thousand dollars but it's
going to last forever and I have ten
thousand people my community for each
willing to put an adult
great can it give water to ten thousand
people and so just look at the actual
solution
and comparing between them being able to
follow and compare all of the amazing
Kickstarter and such campaigns out there
that do solve some of these problems of
water energy generation but being able
to I love seeing videos like this is the
solution look at this cool house made of
like grown-up Lego look at the but like
what does it actually cost to make that
and can I get it transported to me and I
want to know the I don't have to contact
the company myself and get all that
information the next person has to to be
able to compare them for every person on
the planet so I mean since they're not
that complicated but if I'm a village in
Africa what could be said to me because
it doesn't help if it's a solution that
I'm not like I can't get shipped to me
so what's the what's the possibility we
don't need to go that far because our
reservations here have horrible drinking
water in a lot of them and the
government clearly not solving that
problem so as sad as it is it's on the
people to solve it so how can you solve
it how can you get clean drinking water
on the land that you live on and what
are the solutions and part of that is
getting the government involves but
finding ways that you can I don't know
collect rainwater and filter the water
you have for the cheapest possible is a
measure you have right now that you can
do but you know it you know the compare
the ideas for the most cost-effective
the most the ones that are going to last
the longest I think is really important
and it's also very line with finding out
what we have now currently and moving
forward from there